https://founderslosangeles.org/privacy-policy

Skip to secondary content
HomeFounder’s OnlineThis Thing Called Life Radio ShowHistoryWorship ServicesNewsletterFounder’s VoiceAbout UsOur Mission & VisionWhat is Science of Mind (SOM)What We BelieveFAQErnest Inspires Great WorkErnest Holmes as a Creation Spirituality MysticHistoryErnest’s Legacy to Founder’sHistory of New ThoughtLA TourThe Wisdom of the AgesFounder’s Living MuseumThree TreesHow I Met Ernest HolmesSupreme Court LetterOur CommunityMinistersPractitionersSpiritual PracticesPractitioner DirectorySpanish MinistryMinistries & GroupsBoard of TrusteesStaffCommunity PhotosOur YouthProgramsNeed Prayer?Practitioner DirectoryMake a Prayer RequestBuild a PrayerMeditationClassesSOM Accredited ClassesNon-Accredited ClassesWorkshops & SeminarsRegistration & Tuition InfoAfterschool ProgramOur FacilityOur BuildingOur ArchitectYour Wedding at Founder’sFilmingFacilities Rental
Home > Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To send periodic emails
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
© 2020 Founder's Church. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy   Site Map
3281 West 6th Street, Los Angeles, CA 90020 Tel (213) 388-9733
Email info@founderslosangeles.org
